tvfreeload.com 2012-04-11

# Privacy Policy

**TVFreeload.com  
Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy is intended to inform you about the types of information gathered by TV Freeload when you visit TVFreeload.com and/or purchase a TVFreeload.com membership, how we use and safeguard that information, and the degree to which you may control the maintenance and sharing of your information.

**Information Collection  
**When you visit TVFreeload.com, we will not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you choose to provide such information to us.

If you choose to purchase a TVFreeload.com membership, we will ask you to provide certain personally identifiable information such as your name and email address, as well as credit card or other payment information and a billing address. We use this information as required to provide you with your TVFreeload.com membership.

We do not directly collect or store any personal financial information provided in connection with your purchase of TVFreeload.com membership. All personal financial information required to complete your purchase (such as your credit card number) will be provided to and/or collected by a third party vendor who will process payments and complete transactions.

Information collected through tracking and registration will not be shared or sold to third parties for any purpose without your express consent.

**Log Files  
**We may automatically and through third-party tracking services (e.g., Google Analytics) gather certain non-personally identifiable information about your use of TVFreeload.com and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamps, and related data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, solely to improve the quality of our services. Out of respect for your privacy, we do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use both session ID cookies and tracking cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to use TVFreeload.com. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. We use tracking cookies to better understand how you use TVFreeload.com, and to enhance your user experience. A tracking cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You are free to decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to take full advantage of all of our offerings. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while using TVFreeload.com.

**Information Use and Disclosure**  
**Notifications  
**If you choose to purchase a TVFreeload.com membership, we will send you a welcome email including information about TVFreeload.com and confirming your purchase. When you purchase a membership from TVFreeload.com, we will send you an email confirming your purchase.

You may elect to receive emails from us notifying you about new or upcoming products or services, information about changing or updating your registration or payment information, changes to our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy, and promotional materials and offers from our company as well as from our subsidiaries, affiliates, marketing partners, advertisers and other third parties. Out of respect for your privacy, if you no longer wish to receive these emails, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the directions included in each email.

**Disclosure  
**We understand how highly our users value the privacy and security of their personally identifiable information. We will disclose information collected from and about you to the following entities for the following purposes:(1) to our related companies, service providers and suppliers, to enable them to fulfill a product or service request or to perform a business, professional or technical support function for us; (2) as necessary if we believe that there has been a violation of our Terms of Service or of our rights or the rights of any third party; and (3)to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law.

**Business Transitions  
**In the event TV Freeload goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, any personally identifiable information we have on record will likely be among the assets transferred. The transferred personally identifiable information will remain subject to the provisions of this Privacy Policy or any subsequent updated versions.

**Information Security  
**We employ encryption and other security measures to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.Whenever you provide us or our partners with sensitive or confidential information, we or our partners will take commercially reasonable steps to protect such information by establishing a secure connection with your web browser, such as employing a security technology known as a secure-socket-layer (“SSL”) to protect the transmission of such information.

However, please be advised that while we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches from ever occurring. You transmit information to us at your own risk.

**Changes to Privacy Policy  
**We may periodically update this policy. If you are a TVFreeload.com member, we will attempt to notify you of material updates by sending a notice to an email address you may have provided to us. Otherwise, you may view the updated version of this policy on the TVFreeload.com website.

**Contact Us  
**If you have any questions or concerns about this policy, please click here to contact us.

Effective Date: October 1, 2011
